
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">demo</string>
    <string name="android">Android</string>
    <string name="Adesc1">     Android is Open source Linux based Operating System.
        \n\n\nAndroid is a mobile operating system based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software,
        designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets.
    \n \nAndroid is developed by a consortium of developers known as the Open Handset Alliance and commercially sponsored by Google.\n\n</string>


    <string name="cdesc"> Cpp is object oriented programming language.
        \n\n\n\nC++ is a popular programming language.  C++ is used to create computer programs, and is one of the most used language in game development.
        \n\n C++ was designed with an orientation toward systems programming and embedded, resource-constrained software and large systems, with performance, efficiency, and flexibility of use as its design highlights.
    \n\n  C++ has also been found useful in many other contexts, with key strengths being software infrastructure and resource-constrained applications .\n\n</string>


    <string name="jdesc1"> java is high level object oriented programming language.\n\n\nJava is a high-level, class-based, object-oriented programming language that is designed to have as few implementation dependencies as possible.
        \n\nIt is a general-purpose programming language intended to let programmers write once,run anywhere.
       \n\n Java applications are typically compiled to bytecode that can run on any Java virtual machine (JVM) regardless of the underlying computer architecture.
        The syntax of Java is similar to C and C++, but has fewer low-level facilities than either of them.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="pdesc1">   PHP HyperText Preprocessor.\nPHP is server scripting language.\n\n\nPHP is a server scripting language, and a powerful tool for making dynamic and interactive Web pages.PHP is a widely-used, free, and efficient alternative to competitors such as Microsoft ASP.
    \n\n  PHP originally stood for Personal Home Page, but it now stands for the recursive initialism PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor.
       On a web server, the result of the interpreted and executed PHP code – which may be any type of data, such as generated HTML or binary image data – would form the whole or part of an HTTP response.\n\n</string>

    <string name="pydesc1">  python is open source high level programming language.\n\n\nPython is a high-level, interpreted, general-purpose programming language. Its design philosophy emphasizes code readability with the use of significant indentation.
            \n\n     Python is dynamically-typed and garbage-collected. It supports multiple programming paradigms, including structured, object-oriented and functional programming.
        It is often described as a batteries included language due to its comprehensive standard library.\n\n</string>

    <string name="wdesc1">   Wordpress is a free and open source content management system. \n\n\n WordPress is a free and open-source content management system (CMS) written in PHP and paired with a MySQL or MariaDB database with supported HTTPS.
        Features include a plugin architecture and a template system, referred to within WordPress as Themes.
    \n\n  WordPress was originally created as a blog-publishing system but has evolved to support other web content types including more traditional mailing lists and forums, media galleries, membership sites, learning management systems (LMS) and online stores.
       WordPress is a factory that makes webpages  is a core analogy designed to clarify the functions of WordPress: it stores content and enables a user to create and publish webpages, requiring nothing beyond a domain and a hosting service.\n\n</string>
</resources>